<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TrueFast Lenten Practice Guide</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">Intro</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="intro_1">Traditional "celebration" of the season of Lent involves fasting and various kinds of self-denial. The goal is to become less attached to worldly pleasure and more focused on self-examination, penitence and our need for Christ.\n\nThis app is a set of suggested practices inspired by the fasting spoken of by the prophet Isaiah (58:6-14), a fasting from selfishness and oblivousness and passivity:</string>
    <string name="intro_2">Is not this the kind of fasting I have chosen:\nto loose the chains of injustice\nand untie the cords of the yoke,\nto set the oppressed free \nand break every yoke?\nIs it not to share your food with the hungry\nand to provide the poor wanderer with shelter-\nwhen you see the naked, to clothe them,\nand not to turn away from your own flesh and blood?</string>
    <string name="intro_3">Then your light will break forth like the dawn,\nand your healing will quickly appear;\nthen your righteousness will go before you,\nand the glory of the LORD will be your rear guard.\nThen you will call, and the LORD will answer;\nyou will cry for help, and he will say: Here am I.</string>
    <string name="intro_4">If you do away with the yoke of oppression,\nwith the pointing finger and malicious talk,\nand if you spend yourselves in behalf of the hungry\nand satisfy the needs of the oppressed,\nthen your light will rise in the darkness,\nand your night will become like the noonday.\nThe LORD will guide you always;</string>
    <string name="intro_4b">he will satisfy your needs in a sun-scorched land\nand will strengthen your frame.\nYou will be like a well-watered garden,\nlike a spring whose waters never fail.\nYour people will rebuild the ancient ruins\nand will raise up the age-old foundations;\nyou will be called Repairer of Broken Walls,\nRestorer of Streets with Dwellings.</string>
    <string name="intro_5">If you keep your feet from breaking the Sabbath\nand from doing as you please on my holy day,\nif you call the Sabbath a delight\nand the LORD’s holy day honorable,\nand if you honor it by not going your own way\nand not doing as you please or speaking idle words,</string>
    <string name="intro_5b">then you will find your joy in the LORD,\nand I will cause you to ride in triumph on the heights of the land\nand to feast on the inheritance of your father Jacob.\n\nFor the mouth of the LORD has spoken.</string>
    <string name="intro_6">Each week will focus on a different theme taken from this passage.\n\nPratices will include scriptures to read, reflection questions, practical actions, and relevant places to donate money. (If you\'re giving up an indulgence, consider setting aside the money you would have spent and giving it to a worthy cause.)</string>
    <string name="intro_7">Readings and reflections will generally change every day, while other prompts will persist all week.\n\nTap a prompt for details; swipe to dismiss. (Note that if you dismiss a weekly card, it won\'t come back the next day!)\n\nThis is YOUR practice: everything is optional. Do what resonates.\n\n</string>
    <string name="copyright">Scriptures taken from the Holy Bible, New International Version®, NIV®. Copyright © 1973, 1978, 1984, 2011 by Biblica, Inc.™ Used by permission of Zondervan. All rights reserved worldwide. www.zondervan.com The "NIV" and "New International Version" are trademarks registered in the United States Patent and Trademark Office by Biblica, Inc.™.\n\nAll other text by Debra Fournerat and Kristy Overton.</string>
</resources>
